A special greeting to the friends of Traders Point. We
take our disclaimer. We are
not SEBI registered advisors or brokers. Everything we talk about here should be
seen as information only. This is not
our advice to anyone regarding investment or buying or selling shares.
All businesses
have risks. When you understand the risks and
do business with caution,
everything will be fine.
Thank you to all the good hearts who support us.
Live in prosperity, friends. We have come to our Nifty
Next 50 and now we have been
looking at companies that have published results. In that
category, we see ICAI, Lombard General Insurance,
now we see these companies coming and they
are expansive performers in the trend line classifications. If so, then it
is overvalued. That is what
we
get for that stock. Now it is
trading at the current 1604. Here is the
durability score.  They have 60, they are
financially very strong, their
valuation score
is 24, so now this comes, it is a little
overvalued, it is
called an expansive valuation, we saw the trend, it is in
orange color at 47, so
it is a neutral trend, the
analyst came and the price
target is
1559, this comes, it is
still in the Pi zone as far as PE is concerned, we
took this fundamental key matrix, we have interest cover
ratio and current, we have
no data, the current ratio comes, it
is 03, so now this comes, they will have to raise the
current ratio a little more,
because they
have interest cover ratio, do
they need interest cover ratio,
we don't think so,
because they are an insurance company.
Interest is paid only if someone buys it at interest,
but I don't know if there are opportunities for that. The
opportunity is a loss. Return on capital
employed is 19%, return on
equity is 15%, and
insurance companies are taking 15% above. It is a
big deal. At the same time,
we can believe that a company without debt is like that because there is no data on depth to equity.
So now, come to them and come to them, it is
not even in terms of solvency ratio.
Because if they follow only current expenses, it is enough. If they follow only contingencies, it is
enough. At the same
time, they come to them and
take a return. There is no debt. In that case,
this is a very strong company. But the
financials are going to become a little stronger.
Our financials are
strong. Our
view is that at the same time.  PE is 41 and
PP is 65. For us,
this is
overvaluation. This side is
giving one-year forward EPS. They are expecting a 0.1% surprise in their analysis. If we
look at the consensus recommendations, 25 analysts have participated. Out of them, five have come to sell,
five have
held, 18 have come, and 15 have
given a buy.
As for their cash flow, their net cash flow
is growing year-on-year.
Similarly, if we
look at cash from operating income, if we
look at cash from operating activities, it is growing 5% year-on-year. Let's say that we
saw the annual result and saw net
profit year-on-year.  It is in growth, the
net revenue is also in year-
on-year growth. They
are doing everything for Rs 20,000 crore. The most
important thing to look at here is the
current book value of 247, while the
DTM book value is 855. Now this current
book value is 65. Now let's say we
saw that the DTM book value is 855. So, the
price that can be there comes and
runs around 2. 21 runs within that
range. So now when this
comes, the book value
starts to come down. At the same time,
they are only interested in EPS. Even though they
said that, the PE also starts to come down.
As for the quarterly, there
is also a year-on-year quarterly result. The net profit is also positive year-
on-year. At the
same time, the
quarterly revenue is year-on-year.
When you look at it, there is a profit. Now, he has come and
taken revenue even more than last December. Similarly, he has taken profit
even more than December. If you
say that there is a pattern in this, can we get any pattern? After March, he
came and took profit last year. He
came to the first quarter and then came to the second quarter and
also took profit from the second quarter. He
returned and took profit from the third quarter. He returned and took profit in
March.
That is
even more than last year. Okay, this is the same in 2022.
We saw that this has followed. He
took profit in the first quarter and March. He has taken profit in the
first quarter and also in the second quarter. He has taken profit even more than that and made
profit in December.
This is 2022. That is why there is
no pattern this time. It has come in zigzag. The alternative came last time.  There
is a deficit only for December,
so we cannot say anything about the battery.
Now we have already
seen that the book value is 247 DTM, the
book value is
855. Now we have to see if it is going to move to DTM or not. Our value has been corrected. If
we look at the promoters' share holding factor, the
promoters have come and they are still at 51%. There are
no gaps. What have they done? They are at the
same stage as in
March and
December. They are at the same stage.
Only the DIS has
come and made a deficit of almost 1½% to 2%.
It has come from 1516
to 1344. We
can say that they have made a deficit of 2%
now.  We took all this information and
put it in our Excel format.
Here, I came and got a low price and
took 1287. This 1287 is taken. I
took 855 and 15. That's why it
shows 1287. Yes, I took 805 and 15. So
now we came here and
said that if the EPS estimate is annualized, it is
1754. Okay, if we come here and get the DPS estimate and get the DTM
estimate, it is 1754. If we see the EPS
estimate, it is 1808.
So, what is the potential for this year so far?
1754 and
1808. We have these two figures. We
tapped on this figure and
said that we can
go higher. But if we think that there should be a correction, it is from
1520 to 1530.
Until then, we can expect a correction. If you
say that it will come, it will not be the same
day. If you come on the first day and do it, if you do it on the
second day, it will be in
that kind of situation.
Okay, now this is what they come and
say that our 855 DTM book value has come. Then what
happens if EPS comes to 2170? The current
EPS is 2170. Why do they sometimes come and add it to the
next year?
EPS is the
same. EPS is the same, but only the book value changes. When that happens, if they add it to the
next year,
we will come and
mark this figure and add it. If it
goes up, we will see. If it goes up, we will see. If it goes down
1287 is all we
could have taken. We came to
1506 and
1385. We
can expect
this range to fall below. Now we have lifted all these values. We lifted them up.
As soon as we lifted them up, he
is here. Did you see that 1477
came yesterday and
touched the same day yesterday? This one
came in May and came in April.
1754 came in.
47. 1747 is here. We have
marked our 57. So if we
reach that range now, it will be 808. If these
two lines
come together like this and break like that,
this is a good sniper
shot. There will be chances of taking a good lead. Let's see
how far this line has the chances of breaking.
Similarly, if these two
lines
break, this 477 line breaks down and
comes down so far and there
are chances of correcting. If there is a down trend,  Even if
787 comes, it is not surprising.
So now we have marked all these levels. We can mark them and trade as far as we want. We will
come and see if
the information was useful for us.
Shankar is very happy. Thank you to
all the good hearts who support us.
Greetings.